const questions = [
  {
    question: 'How do you call a function named "myFunction"?',
    a: "myFunction()",
    b: "call function myFunction()",
    c: "call myFunction()",
    d: "None of the mentioned",
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
    a: "const",
    b: "var",
    c: "let",
    d: "constant",
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question:
      "When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is",
    a: "Integer",
    b: "Undefined",
    c: "Object",
    d: "Boolean",
    correct: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
    a: "It will debug all the errors in the program at a runtime",
    b: "it acts as a breakpoint in a program",
    c: "it will debug error in the current statement",
    d: "All of the above",
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "What does the ‘toLocateString()’ method do in JS?",
    a: "Returns a localized object representation",
    b: "Returns a localized string representation of an object",
    c: "Returns a parsed string",
    d: "None of the above",
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
    a: "Date",
    b: "FileUpload",
    c: "Function",
    d: "All of the above",
    correct: "d"
  },
  {
    question: " How do we write a comment in javascript?",
    a: "/* */",
    b: "//",
    c: "#",
    d: "$ $",
    correct: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which object in Javascript doesn’t have a prototype",
    a: "Base Object",
    b: "All objects have a prototype",
    c: "None of the objects have a prototype",
    d: "None of the above",
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question:"What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
    a: "async",
    b: "await",
    c: "setTimeOut",
    d: "None of the above",
    correct: "a"
  },
  {
    question:"How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
    a: "intervalOver",
    b: "clearTimer",
    c: "clearInterval",
    d: "None of the above",
    correct: "c"
  }
];

export { questions };
